angryduck.com 2019-06-19

# AngryDuck Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy :**  
angryduck.com does not collect any personal information about its users. Some general information is collected when browsing the site like geographic location, browser and device information used for general understanding of how to best serve our visitors needs. We do not collect any personal information, we do not collect names or addresses, or even email addresses unless you choose to send them to use via our contact form. The information collected about general items regarding your internet and device are collected using google analytics.

**Advertisements**  
“We use third-party advertising companies to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](https://gml.email/v2/lt/df5d27508ee111e8b4a04567549b6659/d2Nod2VzaWtAZ21haWwuY29tfHxodHRwOi8vb3B0b3V0Lm5ldHdvcmthZHZlcnRpc2luZy5vcmc)

**Linked web sites**  
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc.   
Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.   
Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated.   
Check out the FTC's site (1) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.
